vagupu.com 2018-12-21

# Vagupu

This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how Vagupu.com Software Pvt. Ltd. ("Vagupu" or “we”) collect, transmit, and store information about our Users. The term "you" or "You" or “User” or “Users” shall refer to Students, Tutors or any person or entity who views, uses, accesses, browses or submits any content or material to the Site (defined below). This Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights. Providing your information is voluntary and your use of the Site (defined below) after the effective date of this document constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, do not use the Site. 

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect via e-mail, telephone, the website www.Vagupu.com (“Site”), mobile applications, electronic devices and other interactive services. In order to help you get the most out of our service, we collect User submitted personally identifiable information (“PII”) when you use the Site. We ask Site users only to submit the minimum amount of information necessary to use our service. Such information may include your name, address, password, zip code, email address, and phone number for communication purposes. Information may be submitted to the Site or via phone or email when communicating with a Vagupu representative. For students and parents, we may collect information related to your documentation of and payment for tutoring sessions. For tutors, we may collect your Social Security number (SSN) or Federal Employer Identification number (FEIN) and date of birth, for tax purposes or to complete a background check. As detailed in the "Data Transmission and Storage" section below, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption on any page of the Site where we ask you to submit personally identifiable information and encrypt all such information for safe storage in our system. 

We also gather non-PII when you use the Site. Such data is compiled in aggregate and includes things like the referring URL and the type of browser you may be using to access the Site. This data is used to better understand and enhance the user experience on the Site. Vagupu may publish these statistics or share them with third parties without including PII. 

User generated content posted through certain social networking preferences (e.g. pages you "Like" or "Follow") may be viewed by the general public. Accordingly, Vagupu cannot ensure the privacy of any PII included in such User generated content. 

### DATA TRANSMISSION AND STORAGE

Vagupu uses industry-standard 128-bit SSL encryption when collecting and transmitting your information through the Site and the Vagupu network (collectively, the “System.”) Once information has been collected, we encrypt sensitive data in our database for added security. Vagupu also uses firewalls and hardware monitoring across our System to protect against unauthorized access. Unfortunately, even with these measures, Vagupu cannot guarantee the security of PII. By using the Site, you acknowledge and agree that Vagupu makes no such guarantee, and that you use the Site at your own risk. 

### FINANCIAL INFORMATION

If you elect to pay for tutoring lessons with a credit card, we will collect your name, credit card number, expiration date, and address information associated with the account. All financial information is collected and encrypted in our System in full compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard. 

If you are a tutor and elect to pay for a background check, we will collect credit card information to order a background check on your behalf. Payment information entered into our System solely to procure a background check will not be stored on our servers. 

### USE OF COOKIES

Vagupu uses cookies to help create a better user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is sent to your browser from a web server and may be stored on your computer’s hard drive. Vagupu uses cookies to better customize your experience on the Site based on User attributes like your location and account preferences. No personally identifiable information is stored in our cookies. While you may elect to disable or delete cookies from your browser at any time, please note that this action may limit your use of Vagupu services that require cookies. If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you control cookies from being put on your computer to deliver tailored advertising, you may visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s website http://www.networkadvertising.org/ and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance’s website http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. You also can control advertising cookies from Google, by using its Ads Preference Manager. Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into the Site, you may still receive advertisements even if you opt-out of tailored advertising. 

### ONLINE TRACKING

Some browsers allow you to indicate that you would not like your online activities tracked, using "Do Not Track" indicators ("DNT Indicators"), however, we are not obligated to respond to these indicators. Presently, we are not set up to respond to DNT Indicators. This means that while the Site may track certain latent information about your online activities, the collected information will be used to improve your use of our Site and in ways consistent with the provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

### USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Vagupu does not disclose or sell your PII without your consent. We may use PII or other personal information you specifically give to us: a) to provide services to you through the System, b) to process transactions and billing, c) for identification and authentication purposes, d) to communicate with you concerning the System, transactions, security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of the System, e) to improve your response to and interaction with the System, f) to do something you have asked us to do, or tell you of services that we think may be of interest to you; and g) for administration of and troubleshooting regarding the System. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of the System may need access to such information from time to time but are not permitted to disclose such information to others. Vagupu shares a minimum amount of information between tutors and students in order to facilitate the arrangement of tutoring sessions. We reserve the right to release non-personally identifiable information collected in aggregate, however. 

### MINORS

Vagupu does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide your contact information or any other personally identifiable information to Vagupu. If you are the parent or legal guardian of someone under the age of 13 who may have provided us with information without your knowledge or consent, please contact us to have this information removed. All contact, including tutoring sessions, between a tutor and any minor should, of course, take place only in a supervised setting. 

### LEGAL REQUESTS AND BUSINESS TRANSFERS

Vagupu may disclose personal information when we believe such action is necessary to comply with the law or enforce or apply our Terms of Service. In the event of a change in control of Vagupu’s business, personal information may be exchanged as part of a merger, sale, or other business transfer. If such a transfer makes a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you of any changes. 

### YOUR CHOICES

Please remember to help keep the Site secure by never sharing your username or password. If you think your password may have been compromised, please change it immediately or contact Vagupu for additional assistance. 

Vagupu.com may send you email communications periodically detailing new features or promotions on the Site. You may unsubscribe from these messages by using the link at the bottom of the email. We may also send you email messages about the status of your account or any notices as required by law. You may not opt-out of receiving these administrative emails so long as you continue to use this voluntary service. If you wish to terminate your account, please contact us. 

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California law permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed their personal information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year, as well as the type of personal information disclosed to those parties. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please submit your request in an email to [support@vagupu.com](mailto:support@vagupu.com)

### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

Vagupu reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, from time to time, due to modifications to the Site’s features and functionality. We will post any changes here and indicate the new effective date of the Privacy Policy at the bottom of the document. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy for any updates while you are an active User of the Site. 

### USERS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

The Site is hosted in the United States and is governed by United States law. If you are using the Site from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our databases are operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Site, you consent to your information being transferred to our facilities and to the facilities of those third parties with whom we share it as described in our Privacy Policy.
